One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
We're free!
Özgürüz!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Bring down Kaido!
Kaido'yu devirelim!
Hip, hip, hooray!
Bir, 'ki, hurra!
– Hip, hip, hooray!
– Bir, 'ki, hurra!
Luffy!
Luffy!
That was reckless...
Çok patavatsızsın...
Hey.
Hey.
You gonna fight Kaido again?
Kaido'yla yine dövüşecek misin?
Wanna join me?
Bana katılmaz mısın?
Don't be stupid!
Aptal olma!
Just look at my partner to see how that'll go.
Nasıl sonuçlanacağını merak ediyorsan ortağıma bak.
Be thankful I don't kill you here and now!
Seni hemen burada öldürmediğime şükret!
I'm done with alliances.
İttifakların canı cehenneme.
I can't trust anyone anymore.
Artık hiç kimseye güvenemem.
What's that?!
Neler oluyor?!
Let's go, Killer.
Gidelim, Killer.
We're gonna get our crew back.
Tayfamızı geri alacağız.
It's time we go our own way!
Artık bağları koparıp kendi yolumuza bakmanın zamanı geldi!
Warriors' Dream
Savaşçıların Hayali
Look what twenty years can do.
20 yılın getirileri işte bunlar!
Imagine how hard it is to keep believing some pipe dream.
Boş bir hayale inanmanın ne kadar zor olduğunu bir düşünün.
They couldn't even wait ten years...
On yılı bile çıkaramadılar.
They became impatient and advanced on Onigashima.
Bekleyemediler, Onigashima'ya doğru harekete geçtiler.
Everyone died!
Ve herkes öldü!
What in the world happened?!
Neler oldu?!
It's been ten years already!
10 yıl oldu bile!
Ten Years Ago
Yıl Önce
We're all getting older.
Hepimiz yaşlanıyoruz.
If we wait the full twenty years, our vigor will only wane.
20 yıl boyunca beklersek gücümüz azalacak.
Are we really going to wait for people who may never return?!
Belki de hiç dönmeyecek olanları mı bekleyeceğiz cidden?
Believe in Lady Toki's words...! Believe in the retainers!
Toki-sama'nın sözlerine inanın...! O sadık hizmetkârlara güvenin!
Kin'emon will return!
Kin'emon geri dönecek!
Along with Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama yanında olacak!
Since we don't submit to Orochi, we have nothing to eat.
Orochi'ye itaatsizlik etmek, yiyecek bulamamak demektir.
Disease will kill us before a fight does!
Savaş yerine hastalıktan öleceğiz!
It's Kaido's army!
Kaido'nun ordusu bu!
What're you doing to the well?!
Kuyudan ne istedin be?
Shut up!
Kes sesini!
We can't take it anymore, Shutenmaru!
Daha fazla dayanamayız, Shutenmaru!
You can't! You'll die like dogs!
Yeter artık! Köpekler gibi öleceksiniz!
You don't stand a chance without an army under the Kozuki banner!
Kozuki sancağı altında olduğunuz sürece, hiçbir şansınız yok!
We can't take it anymore!
Artık daha fazla dayanamayacağız!
At least let us die holding our swords!
İzin verin, en azından elimizde kılıcımızla ölelim.
If we die, then we do so as samurai!
Öleceksek de birer samuray gibi ölürüz!
Please don't stop us!
Lütfen bizi durdurmayın!
Do you remember when we were children?
Hatırlıyor musun? Çocukken...
We had a cry to test our mettle.
"cesaret testi" dediğimiz şeyi yapardık.
People place too much value on their own lives, which turns them into cowards!
İnsan olduğumuzdan, kendimize değer verdiğimizden dolayı korkarız!
SNATCH!
SUNACCHI!!!
Surrender Names And Thoughts;
İsminizi ve düşüncelerinizi kenara atın.
Cease Hesitations! Then take the plunge!
Tek yapmamız gereken şey;
That's what our yell meant!
Kafamızı boşaltıp düşünmeden dalmak!
Raise your voices! SNATCH!
Bağırın! SUNACCHI!
– SNATCH! SNATCH! SNATCH!
– SUNACCHI! SUNACCHI! SUNACCHI!
Don't do this!
Yapmayın bunu!
If we die, then we do so as samurai!
Öleceksek de birer samuray gibi ölürüz!
– SNATCH! SNATCH! SNATCH!
– SUNACCHI! SUNACCHI! SUNACCHI!
Why did we need to wait twenty years?
Neden 20 yıl beklemek zorundaydık?
We'll know once it's over!
Zaman gösterecektir.
There must be a reason.
Boş yere olmamalı.
I have no reason to doubt Lord Oden.
Oden-sama'dan şüphe etmeyi reddediyorum.
Hey! Men!
Hey, beyler!
In eight days,
Sekiz gün sonra...
on the night of the fire festival,
Ateş Festivali gecesi,
we will raid Onigashima under the Kozuki banner
Kozuki sancağı altında, Onigashima'ya baskın yapacağız...
to take the pirate Kaido and the Shogun Orochi's heads!
ve korsan Kaido'yla şogun Orochi'nin kellesini alacağız!
If you're willing,
Yeterli kararlılığınız varsa,
follow me!
bizimle gelin!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Of course we will, Boss! We've been waiting a long time for this day!
Tabii ki geliriz, patron! Bugün için çok bekledik!
Ashura!
Ashura!
You guys haven't aged since that day, huh?!
O günden beri gram değişmemişsiniz!
We were once the same age, but now we're twenty years stronger!
Bir zamanlar aynı yaştaydık ama şimdi sizden 20 yıl daha güçlüyüz!
Right, you old dog?!
Değil mi, Inu?!
Yes, indeed!
Evet, kesinlikle!
Silence, old timers! Do not get in our way!
Kapayın çenenizi, moruklar! Ayak altında dolanmayın yeter!
Why, you whelp...!
Bak hele şu zibidiye...
Whoa, cut it out! We won't be able to break up a fight among the Red Scabbards!
Hey, kesin şunu! Kızıl kınların kavgasını kimse ayıramaz.
Udon
Udon
A pirate?!
Korsan mı?!
That straw hat guy is a pirate just like Kaido?!
Hasır Şapka, tıpkı Kaido gibi bir korsan mı?!
Yes, but he is different!
Evet ama o farklı!
He's untrustworthy! He'll betray us for sure!
Ona güvenemeyiz! Bize kesinlikle ihanet edecektir!
For crying out loud, why would you bring a damn pirate?!
Sabır yav, ne demeye buraya lanet bir korsan getirdiniz ki?!
Look, the seas are vast, with all sorts of pirates...
Bakın, denizler uçsuz bucaksız, her türden korsanla dolu...
That man is key to defeating Kaido!
Kaido'yu yenmemizin anahtarı o!
Why do we need a pirate?!
Niye bir korsan?!
Explain yourself!
Açıkla hemen!
Oh no, we must have missed something. Everyone's regained their senses, and yet...
Eyvah, bunu düşünemedik. Herkesin kafa yerine geldi ama hâlâ sorunumuz var.
First of all, did you really come from twenty years in the past?
Öncelikle şunu bi' netleştirelim; yirmi yıl geçmişten geldiğine emin miyiz?
Raizo, you've always looked old.
Raizo-san, sen hep yaşlı görünüyordun.
How do we know you haven't just naturally aged twenty years?
Senin doğal yollardan yirmi yıl yaşlanmadığın ne malum?
Even unintentionally, you insult me!
Dolaylı yoldan bana hakaret ediyorsunuz!
Where is Sir Straw Hat?
Bay Hasır Şapka nerede?
Tama, it's dangerous for you to be here.
Tama, burası senin için hiç güvenli bir yer değil.
Forgive me, Big Bro.
Affet beni, ağabey.
But I'm so glad you're okay!
Ama iyi olmana çok sevindim!
Yeah...
Evet...
He's on death's door.
Eceli yanı başında.
What?!
Ne?!
B-Big Bro, you've gotta be strong!
A-Ağabey, güçlü ol!
Don't touch him!
Dokunma ona!
I'll find the antibodies soon enough.
Yakında bir antikor yapacağım.
You shouldn't have pretended that it doesn't hurt!
Canın yanmıyormuş gibi davranmamalıydın.
Painful, isn't it?! Why couldn't you have considered the consequences?!
Canın yanıyor, değil mi?! Sonuçlarını düşünmek çok mu zordu?!
Tell me you're sorry!
Hemen özür dile!
I'm sorry.
Özür dilerim.
It's painful.
Çok acıyor.
Help me.
Yardım et.
Hang on.
Dayan.
We don't need no damn pirates!
Lanet bir korsana ihtiyacımız yok!
Get him out of here!
Çıkarın onu buradan!
Luffy, as dumb as you are, you sure are amazing.
Luffy, aptal olabilirsin ama kesinlikle muhteşemsin.
I could never do something like that.
Ben asla böyle bir şey yapamazdım.
Momo, you...
Momo, sen...
are a real idiot...
tam bir aptal,
and a coward...
korkak,
and a weakling...
güçsüz...
and a wimp...
ve eziğin tekisin!
You're just hopeless.
Umutsuz vakasın.
Shut up, you insolent dog!
Kes sesini, seni küstah köpek!
You have no right to speak to me like that!
Benimle böyle konuşamazsın!
Momo, don't hit him!
Momo-kun, ona vurma!
What are you, a chicken?
Nesin sen... bir tür ödlek mi?
I am Kozuki Momonosuke.
Ben Kozuki Momonosuke'yim.
The son of Kozuki Oden!
Kozuki Oden'in oğluyum!
Then get out there, Momo!
Öyleyse çık karşılarına, Momo!
Banish the pirate!
O korsanı hemen gönderin!
Go already!
Git artık!
S-Stop, you fool! Do you intend to kill me?!
D-Dur, manyak herif! Beni öldürmeye mi çalışıyorsun?!
Who do you think they're waiting for?
Senden başka...
They're waiting for you!
kimi bekliyorlar sanıyorsun?
Is that...? Could it be?
O...? Bu mümkün mü?
Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama!
Thank goodness you're alive!
Hayatta olmanıza çok sevindim!
I see now.
Şimdi anladım.
What was missing...
Eksik olan şey...
was a dream.
bir hayal.
A future... after the war.
Savaştan sonra... yaşanabilir bir gelecek.
It's not me.
Gördükleri ben değilim.
Certainly all they are seeing is my father...
Şu anda Wano'nun yükünü sırtlamış...
the huge shadow cast by the Kozuki that upheld Wano.
Kozuki'nin yüce gölgesini, babamı görüyorlar.
I-I cannot do it...
Y-Yapamam.
I cannot!
Yapamam!
I want to defeat Kaido!
Kaido'yu devirmek istiyorum!
Momonosuke...
Momonosuke...
Do not be afraid, Momonosuke...
Korkma, Momonosuke...
Do not be afraid, Momonosuke!
Korkma, Momonosuke!
Everyone!
Millet!
Please hear me!
Hepiniz beni dinleyin...
What happened that fateful day at Oden Castle?
Oden Kalesi'nde kaderimizin değiştiği o günde ne mi oldu?
Kin'emon, Raizo, Kanjuro, and I embarked on a quest for allies.
Kin'emon ve diğerleriyle müttefik arayışına başladık.
However, I became separated from them in a dangerous place with no way out.
Ama yolda ayrı düştüm; çıkış yolu olmayan tehlikeli bir yerde mahsur kaldım.
I could only return here with the aid of Luffy and his friends, whom we met along the way.
Buraya sadece yolda karşılaştığımız Luffy ve dostlarının yardımıyla dönebildim.
I am still not strong enough...
Hâlâ yeterince güçlü değilim...
but I promise to avenge everyone, no matter the cost!
ama öcünüzü almanıza yardım edeceğime söz veriyorum.
Even through trying times, I carried on and never gave in...
Hepiniz teslim olmayı reddederek zorluklar ve sıkıntılar yaşadınız;
for the sake of one wish.
...tek bir amaç uğuruna.
To fulfill that wish, I need like-minded allies...
Bu amacı gerçeğe dönüştürmek için, benimle aynı fikirdeki müttefiklerin...
I need the help of all like-minded citizens of Wano!
ve Wano'nun tüm sağduyulu vatandaşlarının desteğine ihtiyacım var!
We all share one wish!
Hepimizin ortak bir amacı var...
To take back Wano!
O da Wano'yu geri almak!
I owe all of you my gratitude,
Millet, beni yirmi yıl boyunca beklediğiniz için...
waiting for us to arrive after two decades!
hepinize çok teşekkür ederim!
I am the heir to a daimyo of Wano.
Ben, Wano daimyo veliahtı...
I am Kozuki Momonosuke!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
Now is the time to rise up!
Vakit, ayağa kalkma vaktidir!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Lord Momonosuke's courage sets my heart at ease.
Momonosuke-sama'nın cesareti içimi ferahlatıyor.
I have an urgent matter to attend to. I promise to join you all before the battle.
İlgilenmem gereken mühim bir mesele var. Savaştan önce size katılacağım.
I see. Understood.
Tamamdır, anlaşıldı.
You bastard...
Seni adi...
Is this all of them?
Bu sonuncusu muydu?
How many are there? It's a damn ninja army.
Bunlardan kaç tane var? Lanet ninja ordusu.
Are you injured?
Yaralandın mı?
I'm fine.
İyiyim ben.
I apologize. I have been a burden.
Özür dilerim. Sana büyük bir yük oldum.
You have.
Evet, oldun.
But don't worry about it.
Ama bunun için endişelenme.
If you died, I could never show my face to Momonosuke again.
Ölseydin, Momonosuke'nin yüzüne bakamazdım.
Enma Shrine Deep in a Forest
Ormanın Derinliklerinde Enma Tapınağı
We're heading back to that house in the snow, right?
Karların ortasındaki o eve mi dönüyoruz?
As long as I can hide, anywhere is fine.
Saklanabildiğim sürece her yer olur.
I want to go back to where that guy took my sword.
O adamın kılıcımı aldığı yere geri dönmek istiyorum.
I will gladly show you the way. Bandit's Bridge in Ringo, correct?
Yolu size memnuniyetle gösteririm. Ringo'daki Soyguncu Köprüsü'ydü, değil mi?
I need my missing sword before the battle...
Savaştan önce o kılıca ihtiyacım var.
otherwise my waist won't feel right.
Belimde olmayınca garip hissediyorum.
I guess I made Orochi really mad...
Sanırım Orochi'nin damarına fena bastım...
It's no wonder our pursuers are relentless.
Köpekleri amma da inatçı çıktı!
Otoko... Do you think she'll be okay?
Otoko... Umarım iyisindir...
Yasuie!
Yasuie!
Daddy!
Babacığım!
After such tragedy befell her father...
O feci olaydan sonra yanında olamamak...
I am worried I could not be there for her.
beni gerçekten korkutuyor.
I left her with my crew.
Onu arkadaşlarıma emanet ettim.
She's at least safe from harm.
Olabilecek en güvenli yerde.
I'll never forgive Orochi!
Orochi'yi asla affetmeyeceğim.
I will avenge Tonoyasu, no matter what it takes.
Tonoyasu'nun intikamını alacağım.
I would like... nothing more...
Orochi'yi kendim öldürmekten başka...
than to kill him myself!
hiçbir şey istemiyorum!
You did what?!
Ne dedin ulan?!
You let them get away?!
Kaçtılar mı?!
And the ronin who attacked me?!
Bana saldıran o ronin de mi?!
I am terribly sorry...
Çok üzgünüm.
I am disappointed in you guys!
Beni hayal kırıklığına uğrattınız!
We did capture the man called Trafalgar.
Ama Trafalgar denen adamı yakaladık.
Tra... falgar?
Tra... falgar mı?
Who the hell is that?!
O da kim oluyor be?!
He is a ringleader alongside Straw Hat.
Kendisi Hasır Şapka'nın elebaşıdır.
It means we have captured the two leaders of the invaders.
Bu demek oluyor ki istilacıların iki lideri de artık elimizde.
Where is he now?!
Şimdi nerede?!
In the world of pirates, betrayal never goes out of style!
Korsan dünyasında ihanet çok yaygındır.
Even after torturing him, we can use him in so many ways.
Bir tur işkenceden sonra onu istediğimiz gibi kullanabiliriz.
That sounds good.
Güzel, güzel.
So, how is the capital?
Eee, başkent ne durumda?
Please rest assured.
Lütfen içiniz rahat olsun.
Currently, the city is on high alert,
Şu anda şehir, en üst düzeyde teyakkuzda;
with samurai and ninja on patrol throughout the city.
samuraylar ve ninjalar şehrin her yerinde devriye geziyor.
Until we capture all the invaders,
Hiçbirinin kaçmasına izin vermeyeceğiz.
I shall abide no attempt on your life, Lord Orochi.
Kellenizi almaya çalışamayacaklar bile, efendim.
If you see any of these people, report them immediately.
Bu kişilerden herhangi birini görürseniz derhâl haber verin.
These are all wanted posters?!
Onların hepsi aranıyor posteri mi?!
Know that any attempt to ignore or conceal them will bring conspiracy charges!
Bilin ki bu kişileri saklamak ya da görmezden gelmek, doğrudan komplo suçu sayılacaktır!
We're in a bad spot...
Kahretsin.
We can't go anywhere near the capital anymore.
Bir süre başkentin yakınlarına bile gidemeyeceğiz.
Not just the capital! Those posters are all over the country!
Sadece başkent de değil. Posterler bütün ülkeye dağıtıldı.
Still, in some respect, our job is done in the capital.
Ama sanırım başkentteki işimizi bitirdik bile.
Our objective was to find all the samurai with the crescent tattoos.
Bütün hilal dövmeli samurayları bulduk.
But all those samurai are...
Ama hepsi...
...behind bars now.
...şu anda tutuklu.
Release us immediately!
Bizi hemen serbest bırakın!
Keep quiet!
Sessiz ol!
Tonoyasu's swan song was meant to convince Orochi that those samurai were innocent.
Tonoyasu'nun son fedakârlığı, o samurayların suçsuz olduğunu Orochi'ye kanıtlamak içindi.
Indeed, but it is not as simple as that.
Aynen ama olay o kadar basit değil işte.
The prisoners' quarters are vast. I estimate about a thousand people were caught.
Hapishane çok büyük. Tahminimce bin kişiyi paket etmişlerdir.
Hey, why aren't they releasing these guys?
Hey, neden bu herifleri salmıyoruz?
Do you think Lord Orochi would own up to a mistake?
Orochi-sama bir hata yaparsa bunu kabul edeceğini mi sanıyorsun?
He would never admit to his own blunder.
Hata yaptığını asla kabullenmez.
You're right.
Haklısın.
But now we know that they're our allies...
Tam da müttefik bulduk diye sevinirken...
We need them! We have to do something!
Onlara ihtiyacımız var. Bir şeyler yapmalıyız.
Law's crew should be in there too.
Law'ın tayfası da orada olmalı.
By the way, Shinobu... What're they doing down there?
Bu arada, Shinobu-chan. Orada ne yapıyorlar?
Ah, they're making sky boats.
Ah, hava gemileri yapıyorlar.
Sky boats?
Hava gemileri mi?
It's in preparation for the upcoming Fire Festival.
Yaklaşan Ateş Festivali'ne hazırlık yapılıyor.
Two of their icons just died. It's hard to believe they'd put on a festival.
İki büyük isimleri yeni göçtü, bu hâlde festival patlatmaları çok garip.
Actually, it's just the opposite.
Aslında, olanlar tam da tersi.
The Flower Capital's Fire Festival is an occasion to honor the dead.
Çiçek Başkenti'nin Ateş Festivali, ölülerin yasını tutmak için var.
The more momentous the festivities, the more our thoughts go out to the departed.
Festival ne kadar cafcaflı olursa, ölenlere dair hatıralar da bir o kadar canlanıyor.
Oh? So this festival is pretty important...
Vay be, bu festival bayağı ciddi bir olaymış demek ki...
North of Ebisu Town Outskirts of the Flower Capital
Çiçek Başkenti'nin Kenar Mahallesi Ebisu Kasabası'nın Kuzeyi
I'm glad you're safe!
Şükürler olsun ki iyisiniz!
Yeah, sorry to make you worry...
Evet, sizi endişelendirdiğimiz için özür dileriz.
I heard you all were captured.
Hepinizin yakalandığını duydum.
We were lucky enough to get away.
Paçayı kurtarabildiğimiz için şanslıyız.
Great!
Harika.
Oh, that's right!
Ha, doğru ya.
Take a look at this...
Şuna bir bak...
Before he died, a daimyo named Yasuie...
Yasuie adında bir daimyo, ölmeden önce...
What?! Yasuie?!
Ne?! Yasuie mi?!
While in prison, he drew this symbol and showed it to all the inmates!
...içerdeyken bu sembolü çizip herkese göstermiş!
Wait a minute...
Ama bu farklı...
The snake has two added lines...?
Engereğin karnına iki çizik mi eklenmiş...?
Yeah, that's right!
Evet, aynen öyle!
I guess that changes the meaning of the code.
Sanırım bu durum şifreyi tamamen değiştiriyor.
Those from Wano understood what it meant.
Wano'lular mevzuyu anında çözdü.
It's Yasuie's final message.
Yasuie'nin son mesajı bu.
This is vital!
O hâlde bu bilgi hayati bir öneme sahip!
I'll be sure to pass it on to Kin'emon!
Bunu Kin'emon'a bizzat ileteceğim.
Yes, please do!
Sana zahmet!
Okay!
Tamamdır!
Come to Amigasa Village if you need us.
Bize ihtiyacınız olursa Amigasa Köyü'ndeyiz.
Okay! Give our regards to the others!
Olur! Diğerlerine selamlarımızı iletin!
Captain...
Kaptan...
Captain!
Kaptan!
Your lives are the terms of our exchange.
Hayatlarınız, bu takasın temel şartı.
"Our exchange"? What does that mean?!
Takas mı? Ne demeye çalışıyorsun?!
Should I refuse, then Trafalgar Law...
Reddederseniz, Trafalgar Law...
will come for my life, thus sacrificing yours.
sizinkiyle beraber benim hayatımı da bitirecek.
A threat from a man unwilling to bet on tomorrow...
Yarını düşünmeyen birinden gelen tehdit...
is something that raises concern for my own life.
gerçekten korkulması gereken bir durumdur.
Captain, we're sorry! We screwed up!
Kaptan, bağışlayın bizi! Her şeyi mahvettik!
These three lives belong to you!
Bu canlar sizin!
You're completely free.
Artık tamamen özgürsünüz.
Any objections, Trafalgar?
Sanırım bir itirazın yok, Trafalgar?
No, you can't!
Hayır, yapma!
Don't go! Captain!
Gitme! Kaptan!
Listen, guys.
Dinleyin, çocuklar!
You can never tell the Straw Hat or anyone else that I got caught.
Hasır Şapkalar'a ve samuraylara yakalandığımı asla söylemeyin.
What...? Wh-Why not?!
Ne? N-Neden?!
Captain!
Kaptan!
Wait!
Bekle!
Please don't go!
Lütfen gitme!
Captain!
Kaptan!
I'm sorry...
Özür dilerim...
Everyone... because we messed up...
Millet, kaptanın gidişi...
Captain is...!
bizim suçumuzdu.
We can't just sit around waiting!
Öylece oturup bekleyemeyiz!
We're the Heart Pirates!
Bizler Kalp Korsanları'yız!
Let's take our captain back!
Kaptanımızı geri alacağız!
His life is more important than Kin'emon's plan!
Onun hayatı Kin'emon'un planından daha önemli!
Trafalgar Law!
Trafalgar Law!
You bastard...
Seni adi...
Leave it at that.
Bırak onu.
What's wrong? You've been acting strangely.
Sorun nedir? Tuhaf davranışlar sergiliyorsun.
It's nothing.
Bir şey yok.
Let's make this quick.
Bu işi çabucak halledelim.
Yeah, it's an easy job.
Evet, tereyağından kıl çeker gibi.
We'll be done as soon as you sing.
Öttüğü an işimiz bitmiş olacak.
Your crew is allied with the Straw Hats.
Hasır Şapkalar'la bir ittifak içindeler.
What could you all possibly be planning here in Wano?
Wano'da tam olarak ne yapmayı planlıyorsunuz?
Tell us everything.
Her şeyi paşa paşa anlatacaksın.